

VICKY FAHREZA RACASIWI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



Pondok Asri Indah Blok C2 No.8 - BATAM



vickyfrzaa



087832495551

PERSONAL PROFIL

A fresh graduate from Binus University majoring in Computer Science that having the integrity to build new experiences within new challenging circumstances for my future career. Being able to contribute with the company based on my skills.

SKILLS

Languages

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

PHP

Python

Framework / System

Bootstrap

Jquery

Responsive Web & Mobile

GitHub

Codeigniter

MVC

Software & Hardware

Odoo

Laravel

Database

DBMS

MySql

HeidiSQL

EDUCATION

vickyfahreza23@gmail.com

Binus University

COMPUTER SCIENCE | 2016 - 2021

- learn Data Structure
- Learn OOP
- Learn Databse
- Web Programming

WORKING EXPERIENCE

PT. GED Lintas Indonesia Web Developer

JAKARTA | JUNI 2021 - AGUSTUS 2021

- Create a website for later vendors to use to check all the history of goods that have been sent
- Making the website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Jquery, for the Backend using PHP CI3 and the database using HeidiSQL

Sentral Cargo

Web Developer & IT Support

JAKARTA | SEPTEMBER 2019 - APRIL 2020

- Create an internal inventory website for employees
- Making the website using HTML, CSS as the frontend and PHP Native as the Backend and also MySql as the database using PHPMyAdmin
- Being IT Support that helps employees such as repairing LAN, assembling 1 SET of computers to be used in branch offices, repairing hardware and software.

Kominfo

FrontEnd Developer

TANGERANG | MARET 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2019

- Creating a website display for one of the districts in Tangerang
- Make the website look using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap

ADDITIONAL

- English Course
- Certificate Altera Academy